<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<ballet>
    <shoe>
        <name>Split Sole Canvas Ballet Shoe</name>
        <brand>Alegra</brand>
        <opis>
            The Alegra split sole canvas ballet shoe. 
            This ballet shoe features a suede split sole, canvas upper and two cross elastics pre-sewn. 
            The cotton lining and elastic drawstring for a secure and comfortable wear.
        </opis>
        <link>https://eu.movedancewear.com/alegra-split-sole-canvas-ballet-shoe-p3721/</link>
    </shoe>
    <shoe>
        <name>Elastosplit ES0251L Split Sole Ballet Shoe</name>
        <brand>Bloch</brand>
        <opis>
            Ultra comfortable and innovative "Elastosplit" ballet shoes from Bloch. 
            Perfect for use as ballet shoes with unnecessary materials removed to provide the perfect window to your arch. 
            These are latest version the "Elastosplit 2", a revised design improves the fit of the dance shoe.
        </opis>
        <link>https://eu.movedancewear.com/bloch-elastosplit-es0251l-split-sole-ballet-shoe-p321/</link>
    </shoe>
    <shoe>
        <name>Freeform Split Sole Shoe</name>
        <brand>Capezio</brand>
        <opis>
            Fantastic dance shoe suitable for contemporary, jazz, modern and ballet. 
            This Capezio shoe has a leather and Lycra mix upper, with a sculpted, seamless, powermesh arch. 
            The contoured cushioned suede sole patches add comfort, and the plush elastic topline keeps the shoe in place. 
            The back elastic is adjustable.
        </opis>
        <link>https://eu.movedancewear.com/capezio-freeform-split-sole-shoe-p1396/</link>
    </shoe>
    <shoe>
        <name>Teaching Ballet Shoe</name>
        <brand>Freed</brand>
        <opis>
            From Freed of London, this teaching shoe has a low block heel for comfort, and a soft leather upper with cross straps.
        </opis>
        <link>https://eu.movedancewear.com/freed-teaching-ballet-shoe-p1657/</link>
    </shoe>
    <shoe>
        <name>Stella Split Sole Ballet Shoe</name>
        <brand>Merlet</brand>
        <opis>
            A new ballet shoe from Merlet. 
            Developed with an elastic canvas for a fantastic fit. 
            The low vamp and elastic edge makes it suitable for all dancers of all levels.
        </opis>
        <link>https://eu.movedancewear.com/merlet-stella-split-sole-ballet-shoe-p3082/</link>
    </shoe>
    <shoe>
        <name>Full Sole Satin Ballet Shoe</name>
        <brand>Move Dance</brand>
        <opis>
            A gorgeous satin ballet shoe from our Move Collection, great for shows and performances. 
            Soft cotton lining, a full suede sole and a drawstring topline for a comfortable wear. 
            The elastic is already attached for your convenience.
        </opis>
        <link>https://eu.movedancewear.com/move-dance-full-sole-satin-ballet-shoe-p2619/</link>
    </shoe>
    <shoe>
        <name>Soft Split Sole Ballet Shoe</name>
        <brand>Repetto</brand>
        <opis>
            From Repetto, a soft canvas ballet shoe in petal pink colour. 
            For a basic – intermediate dancer, with a split sole and pre-sewn cross-over elastics. 
            The triangle montage design in the sole helps accentuate the arch of the foot, and emphasises ‘cou-de-pied’ work.
        </opis>
        <link>https://eu.movedancewear.com/repetto-soft-split-sole-ballet-shoe-p3013/</link>
    </shoe>
    <shoe>
        <name>Tutu Split Sole Canvas Ballet Shoe</name>
        <brand>Sansha</brand>
        <opis>
            A great basic ballet shoe from Sansha, with cotton lining, single sewn elastics, and a split sole.
        </opis>
        <link>https://eu.movedancewear.com/sansha-tutu-split-sole-canvas-ballet-shoe-p1747/</link>
    </shoe>
    <shoe>
        <name>SD16 Stretch Split Sole Canvas Ballet Shoe</name>
        <brand>So Danca</brand>
        <opis>
            These nude split sole canvas stretch ballet shoes from So Danca are lightweight and extremely flexibile. 
            The breathable stretch fabric plus the split sole enhances a range of movement with little resistance despite the tight fit. 
            Two crossover elasticated straps, and elasticised fabric, 
            improve the fit of the shoe with the added benefit that the elastic is more comfortable than a drawstring shoe. 
            These shoes exaggerate and contour your arches, creating a gorgeous foot on stage to be noticed even in nude.
        </opis>
        <link>https://eu.movedancewear.com/so-danca-sd16-stretch-split-sole-canvas-ballet-shoe-nude-p4582/</link>
    </shoe>
    <shoe>
        <name>Full Sole Satin Ballet Shoe - Ivory</name>
        <brand>Tappers &amp; Pointers</brand>
        <opis>
            An elegant and classic ballet shoe from Tappers &amp; Pointers. Ivory satin with a full sole, ideal for the beginner dancer.
        </opis>
        <link>https://eu.movedancewear.com/tappers-and-pointers-full-sole-satin-ballet-shoe-ivory-p818/</link>
    </shoe>
    <shoe>
        <name>Split Sole Ballet Shoe - Black</name>
        <brand>Basilica</brand>
        <opis>
            Show your personality and a flash of colour as you dance with Basilica's canvas split sole ballet shoes. 
            The sole of the shoes features a unique floral pattern insert on the arch that makes your shoes even more dainty and feminine. 
            The vibrant, realistic roses pattern looks pretty against the black canvas backdrop. 
            Part-sewn elastics will make preparing your shoes for dance class even quicker. 
            Canvas material plus the cotton lining creates a breathable shoe that will dry well after an intense ballet rehearsal.
        </opis>
        <link>https://eu.movedancewear.com/basilica-dancewear-split-sole-ballet-shoe-black-p4799/</link>
    </shoe>
</ballet>